[
  {
    "prompt": "Cute",
    "answers": ["귀엽다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Long",
    "answers": ["길다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Slim, thin",
    "answers": ["날씬하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tall, big",
    "answers": ["크다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Diet",
    "answers": ["다이어트"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Strong, robust",
    "answers": ["튼튼하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Weight",
    "answers": ["몸무게"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same",
    "answers": ["똑같다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fat, overweight",
    "answers": ["뚱뚱하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Skinny, gaunt",
    "answers": ["마르다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Appearance",
    "answers": ["모습"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Height",
    "answers": ["키"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Voice",
    "answers": ["목소리"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Similar",
    "answers": ["비슷하다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Short",
    "answers": ["짧다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Young",
    "answers": ["젊다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Pretty",
    "answers": ["예쁘다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Small",
    "answers": ["작다"]
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Handsome, good looking",
    "answers": ["잘생기다"]
  }
]
